<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Just Stay In Bed</title>
    <link>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Just Stay In Bed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 08:46:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of Sleeping on a Natural Latex Mattress</title>
      <link>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/latex-mattress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/latex-mattress/</guid>
      <description>Latex is a natural material derived from the sap of the rubber tree and is then transformed into latex foam used in natural latex mattresses. Latex mattresses offer great comfort and maximum support as they conform instantly to every movement keeping the spine and back in the correct position and relieving pressure points at the same time. Natural latex mattresses have great elasticity, yet they are very durable. A latex mattress will outlast any other conventional, pocket sprung or memory foam mattress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not All Organic Mattresses Are Made Equal</title>
      <link>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/organic-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/organic-video/</guid>
      <description>Highest Standards While many mattresses make claims about how they are made and what types of materials aren’t used in the process, PlushBeds mattresses backs up their claims with various certifications. Our certifications are from respected, independent certifying agencies, including:  Global Organic Latex Standard (latex) Global Organic Textile Standard (cotton and wool) USDA Organic (latex, cotton, and wool) GreenGuard Gold Certification Oeko-Tex Standard 100 Eco-Institut Certification Control Union Certification Forest Stewardship Council Certification  We believe that by going through the process of meeting multiple standards, we’re providing better products for you, our customers, and the planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not All Organic Mattresses Are Made Equal</title>
      <link>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/sale-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/sale-video/</guid>
      <description>Highest Standards While many mattresses make claims about how they are made and what types of materials aren’t used in the process, PlushBeds mattresses backs up their claims with various certifications. Our certifications are from respected, independent certifying agencies, including:  Global Organic Latex Standard (latex) Global Organic Textile Standard (cotton and wool) USDA Organic (latex, cotton, and wool) GreenGuard Gold Certification Oeko-Tex Standard 100 Eco-Institut Certification Control Union Certification Forest Stewardship Council Certification  We believe that by going through the process of meeting multiple standards, we’re providing better products for you, our customers, and the planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixelato</title>
      <link>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/testpage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/testpage/</guid>
      <description>pixelato</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PlushBeds</title>
      <link>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/organic_mattress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/organic_mattress/</guid>
      <description>*Did you know that you could be risking your and family’s health just by going to sleep?* Yes, you read that correctly. The very place you come to for refuge at the end of the day, could actually be bad for you!
Many mattresses on the market have a slew of harmful toxins. Most mattresses actually, and your mattress may be one of your most significant daily sources of chemical exposure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PlushBeds</title>
      <link>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/plushbeds_about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/plushbeds_about/</guid>
      <description>PlushBeds is a leading manufacturer and retailer of natural and organic luxury mattresses, designed to eliminate harmful chemicals and facilitate quality sleep. All of PlushBeds mattresses are made with toxin-free materials; certified with GreenGuard Gold status and they meet flammability standards without the need for chemical flame retardants. GOLS, GOTS, GreenGuard Gold Certified.
You’ll be amazed at how well you’ll feel when you upgrade to an organic, restful sleep on a latex mattress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PlushBeds</title>
      <link>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/plushbeds_certifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/plushbeds_certifications/</guid>
      <description>Certifications and Tests PlushBeds is committed to providing you with the best and most healthy sleep products on the market. In order to achieve this, PlushBeds ensure that their products and their business meet the high standards of the most rigorous tests and certifications in the industry. Learn more about all oftheircertifications below.
Less than 1% of Mattresses Can Match Our Purity Certifications.
Safety and Sustainability Standards Global Organic Latex Standard (GOLS)    The Global Organic Latex Standard (GOLS) is the materials and processing standard for organic latex and finished organic latex foam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why a Natural Mattress is a Healthier Mattress</title>
      <link>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/natural-mattress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/natural-mattress/</guid>
      <description>The average person spends eight or more hours, sleeping in their bed, every night. When you think about it, that adds up to one-third of their lifetime. Your mattress is an intimate point of contact, and it could be a huge health risk for you and your family if you’re not using a natural mattress. Absence of Toxic Chemicals Some mattresses on the market today, contain chemicals that can have toxic effects on humans, when they off-gas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sleepsuppliers.com/posts/store/</guid>
      <description>#shrs_MAP60673_target { text-align: center; width: auto; margin: 5px; border-style: solid; padding: 4px; border-width: 2px; border-color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; height: auto; } #shrs_MAP60673_pagingDsp { font-size: 1.2em; font-weight: bold; text-align: center; } #shrs_MAP60673_pagingDsp ul.shrs_MAP60673_pagingList { padding: 0px; margin: 5px 0px 0px; } #shrs_MAP60673_pagingDsp ul.shrs_MAP60673_pagingList li { display: inline; list-style-type: none; padding-right: 10px; } #shrs_MAP60673_pagingDsp ul.shrs_MAP60673_pagingList li.shrs_MAP60673_currentPage { font-size: 1.3em; font-weight: bold; } #shrs_MAP60673_pagingDsp ul.shrs_MAP60673_pagingList li a { color: rgb(0, 82, 156); } #shrs_MAP60673_pagingDsp ul.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>